carreview.com 2006-04-13

# Consumer Product Reviews - ConsumerREVIEW.com

ConsumerREVIEW.com is committed to protecting your privacy and the personal information that you provide to us. Please read the Privacy Policy below to understand how we collect, use, and treat your personal information. If after reviewing this Privacy Policy you have questions regarding our treatment of your personal information, please send your questions to privacy@consumerreview.com .  

**What this Privacy Policy covers**  
This Privacy Policy covers the personal information that ConsumerREVIEW.com collects from you or about you on our community of Websites , and any personal information that our partners may share with us.   

This Privacy Policy does not cover the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or the actions of people that ConsumerREVIEW.com does not employ or manage.   

**Information Collected by ConsumerREVIEW.com**  
ConsumerREVIEW.com collects personal information from you when you register to write a review, or register to enter a sweepstake, contest or survey on our Web site. We will only collect your personal information if you choose to share it with us. When you register with ConsumerREVIEW.com, we ask for your email address, first name, last name, password, hometown and zipcode. Your registration information is stored in a database at ConsumerREVIEW.com. If you enter a sweepstakes, contest or survey we may also ask you for some demographic information such as your age or income level. We may also receive information about you from our business partners.   

ConsumerREVIEW.com also automatically records non-personal information including your Internet Protocol address, browser format and system information on its Web server logs.   

Other companies which place advertisements on our pages or offer products on our Web site may collect information about you when you click on their content. Any information collected by these companies is not subject to this Privacy Policy.   

**How ConsumerREVIEW.com Uses the Information Collected**  
We use the information we collect from you to confirm the validity of submitted reviews, contact winners of sweepstakes or contests, customize our services, improve the content of our Web site, provide you with our newsletter and notify you about our products and services. ConsumerREVIEW.com may also use the information for internal purposes, such as studying our viewers' preferences.   

We use the information collected regarding the activity on our Web site (such as the number of viewers and the pages commonly visited) on an anonymous basis. We may aggregate this anonymous information and use it to improve our products and services.   

**Information that is Shared or Disclosed**  

  * ConsumerREVIEW.com does not sell or license your personal information.   

  * We may share your personal information with business partners who work on behalf of ConsumerREVIEW.com to provide you with a product or service. These business partners may only use your personal information to assist ConsumerREVIEW.com, and are prohibited from using your personal information for other purposes.   

  * We may disclose anonymous aggregate information (for example, the percentage of our viewers that visit the product review section of our Web site) to third parties such as our advertisers or business partners.   

  * ConsumerREVIEW.com will also disclose personal information about its viewers when the law requires it, such as when we respond to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process.   

  * In the event that ConsumerREVIEW.com merges with or is acquired by another business entity we may share some or all of your information with the new entity in order to continue to provide you with our products and services.   

**ConsumerREVIEW.com's use of Cookies**  
ConsumerREVIEW.com sets and accesses cookies on your computer while you are on our community of Web sites. We use cookies to determine whether you have been to our Web site before, to save your password, and for advertising efficiency. ConsumerREVIEW.com cannot access any cookies on your computer except for those set by us.   

Companies which place advertisements on our pages or offer products on our Web site may set and access their cookies on your computer while you are on our Web site. The use of cookies by these companies is not subject to this Privacy Policy   

**Children Under 13**  
ConsumerREVIEW.com's Web site is not designed for children under 13\. If we discover that you are under 13 and have registered with us, we will delete your registration.   

Companies which place advertisements on our pages or offer products on our Web site may set and access their cookies on your computer while you are on our Web site. The use of cookies by these companies is not subject to this Privacy Policy   

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
ConsumerREVIEW.com may change how we collect, use or treat your personal information. Please check back periodically to review any changes that we have made to the Privacy Policy.   

Should ConsumerREVIEW.com make any material changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our homepage at   [www.ConsumerREVIEW.com](http://www.consumerreview.com/) .
